LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate the face of light
Save your tears for the day
when our pain is far behind
on your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
F-4 decoys activated!
Barrier dismantling viruses injected!
Good.
Once you've put our offensive firewalls
on standby at all the external firewalls,
activate protection and freeze it.
Roger!
Found it.
So, a stealth gate that must traverse Europe's
satellite network via the northern hemisphere...
Yeah.
But it's nothing serious.
It's actually an Asian matrix.
So, a local Asian net.
Not sophisticated at all.
Nope.
Shall we begin the structural analysis right away?!
Contact the Major first.
To Those
Without Even
a Name
Gouda's showing off, isn't he?
It's a message that we won't
find proof that leads to him
even if we find Kawashima's external memory.
How clever.
However, from the looks of it,
there is no trace that a third party
has tampered with this external memory.
If we are to presume that the Individual
Eleven phenomenon is the result of a virus,
there is a significant
chance that evidence remains.
All right, I'll dive.
Ishikawa and Bomer, cover me.
Tachikoma, have the viral array on standby.
How about the D set?
That's fine.
Major, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I need you ASAP.
This is top priority.
Since it has higher priority than
this, it can't be good.
That's right.
Call Batou, Saitou and Pazu as well.
You heard him.
Bomer, make the dive in my place.
Ishikawa, please take care of the rest.
All right, let's get this over with.
Let's go.
Hey, hey.
Togusa-kun, why don't you put
your personified data on default?
Huh?
Well, it may be different if
we're talking about chats.
but don't you think it'd be too dangerous
to lug something heavy like that around
when you're diving into a firewall array?
Besides, do you really want to see me and
old man Ishikawa looking out of place,
wearing costumes like
American comic book heroes?
You have a point there...
Cut the chit-chat.
Bomer's about to go through the gate.
Resuming viral injection!
Collision with enemy's firewall array and
commencement of neutralisation confirmed.
How is it going?
It's starting to become visible.
There's a suspicious file on level six.
What's the name of the file?
"Individual Eleven."
What now?
Then, if we are to confirm whether that's the
virus that triggers the Individual Eleven,
It'd be quickest to drop that
file into someone's cyberbrain.
Hey...
Oh well.
I guess I'll try putting it in my head.
Hey, isn't it dangerous?
Wouldn't it be better to build a vaccine first?
You can't make vaccines
until after symptoms develop.
That's how it is.
All right, the backup is complete.
Just in case, partition off your
cyberbrain's analysis sectors.
Yep.
This is footage that was recorded twenty-two minutes
ago by the IR system on Nagasaki's offshore reef.
Man, where has he been hiding all this time?
If he hadn't switched to a new cybernetic body,
it could be that he was inactive
until his body parts regenerated.
This could be our chance.
I have requested that the authorities in Kyushu
bolster their surveillance of the entire region.
Go to Nagasaki ASAP and secure him!
Hey, Bomer...
You okay?
Hey, isn't this bad?
We'll terminate the program by force.
Hey, Bomer!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
So, how was it?
Nothing special.
The contents were a poorly constructed essay.
Essay?
If that man is the same one who
attacked the Prime Minister,
then as the Chief said,
it's quite possible that the factor
that caused the Individual
Eleven's appearance is still
fully retained in his cyberbrain.
We could use long distance sniping,
but PKF-spec bodies are immortal prosthetics whose
organs each operate independently.
They can't be stopped unless
you shoot them in the head.
If that's the case, we'll get
close and overwhelm him by force.
Depending on the situation, I can
use this and just take the head back.
Quite a sadist, aren't you?
I wonder if symptoms won't develop
just by downloading this thing...
After all, there's no point in
randomly scattering this around
and turning everyone into an Individual Eleven.
It could be that there are other factors involved.
How's it going?
Not very good.
Gouda's plans, which the Major found
after diving in, were very credible.
His plans ignited the fury of the refugees.
He's responsible all right.
In addition, it seems he can't wait to
have someone else discovers his methods.
But, unless he displays
symptoms, we can prove nothing.
If we could at least get our hands on the
original "Individual Eleven" essay...
But they couldn't find it the last
time they searched either, right?
Then how about trying to find it in paper?
The original document may
still be around somewhere.
True.
I have a place in mind.
Try there.
Understood.
All right, I'll leave that to you.
Bomer and I will do another complete
analysis on Kawashima's external memory.
It's the only lead we have right now.
All right, I'm counting on you two.
Let's go.
Okinawa Prefecture Monument
Foreign War
Casualties Monument
Stop that.
Save these feelings for the
actions we'll be taking.
I concur.
It seems the others are also gathering.
We don't have time.
We lost track of him?
Yes.
We were able to confirm from the highway's
IR system that he headed towards Kagoshima,
but after he pulled over at a rest stop, he
may have switched his car to remote control,
then hid himself in a freight
truck heading elsewhere.
The staff from the monitoring centre appear
to have continued their pursuit of the car.
Where did his car go after that?
The car left the interchange
and went towards Fukuoka.
What about hacking the car's
AI and putting a trace on him?
The moment we tried to connect,
the network got cut off.
So he knows something about cyberspace warfare.
I see.
Pursue all the freight trucks that
appear in this footage and find him.
Understood.
What now?
We will head to Kagoshima.
And what if this a trap he
rigged to make you think that?
If we consider the possibilities,
Kagoshima is highest on the list.
Kagoshima Prefecture War
Casualties Monument Tower
Is this everyone?
Anyone who shares the particularist
will would not arrive any later.
Niihama University
Sociology Department
I came with Chief Aramaki's recommendation.
My name is Togusa.
Yes, I've heard of you.
You wanted to see the original
"Individual Eleven." correct?
Yes. I couldn't find it on the net,
no matter how hard I looked, so...
Not surprisingly.
The "Individual Eleven" is a very
valuable book by Patrick Sylvestre
written after he invested himself
in the Romanian Revolution
right before his death.
Only twenty copies were published.
A significant number of translated editions
should have been reprinted by now, though.
The author himself seems to
have locked the text away
because he couldn't conclusively define the 515 Incident
in Japan as having been a revolution until the very end.
I have heard that his thought processes, which
include using Noh as a metaphor for revolution,
still retain their brilliance today.
It doesn't seem like you're
here with a snobby attitude.
Very well.
Since you do also have Aramaki-san's referral I'll
make a special exception and show it to you.
Thank you.
How is it going?
Well, I think I got him to trust me.
That aside, I'm surprised that this stuffy
professor is an acquaintance of yours.
Times may change,
but it'll always be about networking.
True.
How strange...
I'd never taken it out of this
room since I obtained it, but...
Um, it doesn't have to be the original.
It can be a copy or a reprint...
Well, for some reason,
I see no sign of it at all.
By the way, how did you assert yourself?
I just stabbed an enemy of the state, a Diet member who
was advocating a conciliatory policy towards refugees.
And you?
We infiltrated the JNN TV accounting network
and made it seem as though they were misappropriating funds
that were set aside for charities assisting refugees.
Oh?
We used a more direct approach to
prompt the liberation of refugees.
The bombing of the refugee support organisation,
Kinan Association, was how we asserted ourselves.
The media gave a lot of press to
the Kinan Association bombing,
but all it did was to sever ties between refugees.
We got rid of a true enemy of the state, a traitor.
We targeted the NPO that was providing
refugees with free cybernetic bodies.
Though it seems you failed to
carry out a successful bombing.
Certainly, striking down a traitor is amusing too,
but what matters is severing the arteries of the
refugees who ought to be liberated.
What have you done, then?
I took the netbank president's head.
You're the one who got President Jima Ichihiro, who
made his fortune through the netbank he created,
even though he was born a refugee?
While I haven't done as much as you in the way
of severing these so-called support lines,
in terms of having an impact on the public, what
I've done does not take a back seat to you.
I am the one who killed the
popular cyber-rapper, "Densetsu".
And one more thing:
I also spread the rumour that the
refugees would try to take the fuel rod
that was dug up from the
government's secret nuclear plant.
Impressive.
Those events did in fact have a major impact
on both the citizens and the refugees.
Densetsu was a pillar of psychological
support for the refugee youths.
It was natural that hatred took root in
their hearts when he was lost to them.
On top of that, you spread a rumour
that would incite a mass uprising.
Our actions pale in comparison to yours.
Unfortunately, yes.
However, in terms of how we severed the
refugees' support, by killing a physician
who was an enemy of the state,
the significance is the same.
How have you asserted yourself?
I tried to assassinate Kayabuki.
Hah.
You chose a very audacious act.
However, I've never heard of this incident.
It must have been ignored, as were the
Individual Eleven's claims of responsibility.
That is of trivial importance.
That aside, this liberation of the refugees you all
speak of only seems to lead them to despair...
why is that?
It is to cut off support from enemies
of the state and their compatriots,
and prompt the liberation known as independence.
That is the best way to have citizens realise on their own
the existence of the foreign entity called the refugees.
Is this not true?
Hey, Ishikawa.
Have you read all of Sylvestre's essays?
Yeah, all of them except
the "Individual Eleven."
Why do you ask?
What about you, Chief?
I actually haven't read any.
I've also read all of them aside
from the "Individual Eleven."
Well, it'd be more unusual that someone
would've read all of them in this day and age.
Yeah.
But this Kawashima has read them too.
Not only that, but he must have
uploaded them to his external memory
and memorised every word.
Oh?
What is it?
I get it.
So that's the factor that activates the virus.
Probably.
Tachikoma, from that external
memory, collect files that pertain
to Sylvestre's collection of
preliminary theories on revolution.
Roger!
Major, I found him!
it's an image of Kagoshima Prefecture's War
Casualties Monument Tower that was taken at 14:30.
All right, change direction towards
the War Casualties Monument Tower!
Understood, heading towards the
War Casualties Monument Tower.
Chief, no luck here.
The "Individual Eleven" isn't here, either.
If it isn't there,
there are no further means of finding it, it seems.
Togusa, come back for now.
If we can't find it, we can't find it.
Yeah...
But I have one more place in mind.
I'll come back after checking it out.
All right.
We've extracted the files!
All right, let's have a go at it.
Roger.
It's almost time.
Yeah.
By the way, who will deliver the final speech?
The one who was able to propagate our intent the
most would be the one most suitable for the task.
That would be...
you, I presume?
Among our comrades who did not show up,
I am sure that there are many
who contributed to our cause,
but if all of you feel I should, then I
will willingly accept that monumental task.
You don't have any objections, do you?
None.
However, I have one request.
Our scripture, the "Individual Eleven."
If you don't object, could I see yours?
Is yours the first edition?
A moment.
If you wanted to know the edition, mine should
be the first edition, if I recall correctly.
Are you sure?
Y-Yeah.
Today, as I proceeded to make my way here,
I decided to bring a copy of the
"Individual Eleven" with me.
But no matter how hard I
looked, I couldn't find it.
Why is that?!
Please, will someone please let
me see the "Individual Elev...
Hey.
We're almost there.
Window Sign: Dobashi Fumiya Office
Y-You're that guy from before.
You're in quite a hurry, aren't you?
I actually had another
question to ask of you.
You came at just the right time.
In any case, come with me!
H-H-Hey!
Stop it! Put that down!
Please stop!
What are you doing?!
How is it?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Maybe we do need the original of the
last essay, the "Individual Eleven."
"Individual Eleven"
What the?
Ishikawa!
Bomer!
Tachikoma, turn off Bomer's cyberbrain
activity and have him sleep.
Also, make that file unreadable and
seal it off with a firewall array.
Roger!
Looks like we got lucky.
Chief, we have an emergency transmission
from the Ministry of the Interior.
Put it through to the Dive Room!
Roger.
This is...
What the hell were they
doing in a place like this?
Major, go to the Kyushu Communications Tower ASAP!
He showed up there!
What is this about?
I don't know, but Channel W3 has him on camera.
So they found him?
Hey, what'd they say?
What'd they say?!
Bring the camera around!
What the hell?
Oh my god, swords!
They're swinging their swords... OH MY GOD!
Their heads...
They cut off... each other's heads...
with their swords!
One after the other... Th... they're fighting!
It's an unbelievable sight!
The men who appeared on the building's rooftop
seem to have killed each other with swords!
Please calm down, I just came here to talk.
Don't come any closer.
You know the essay titled the
"Individual Eleven", right?
That "Individual Eleven" essay...
never existed in the first place!
All that exists... is a manufactured
theory called the "Individual Eleven"!
I am the Individual Eleven!
The time has finally come!
An ambulance, hurry!
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(the time is right)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
all I need,
to make all this